millerslab.com 2012-05-23

# Privacy Policy

## Miller’s Professional Imaging Co Privacy Policy

Miller’s Professional Imaging Co. (hereinafter “Miller’s”) is committed to safeguarding your privacy on its websites Millerslab.com, Millersalbums.com, Millersevents.com, and mpix.com (individually and collectively the "Site") This Miller’s Privacy Policy does not apply to products or services provided, or information obtained, other than through the Site.  Please read the following policy to understand how your information will be treated. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically.  Please keep in mind that some of the services mentioned specifically in this policy may not be available on the site at this time.  If you have questions concerning this policy, please contact Dick Colman **** at dickc@millerslab.com. **  **This Privacy Policy is effective as of July 31, 2007.

## What information may Miller’s collect from me?

Miller’s collects information in several ways. For example, some personal information is gathered when you register as a customer using our account interface. During registration, we may ask for your Miller’s Account Number and your email address. Once you register, you are no longer anonymous to Miller’s and are able to take full advantage of our services. In addition to registration, we may ask you for information at other times, such as when you report a problem with our site or services, or contact the company via the corporate e-mail address. If you contact Miller’s, we may keep a record of that correspondence. ****

If you believe that any inaccurate or inappropriate information has been obtained or disseminated through your use of this Site, you should contact a representative of Miller’s at [custserv@Millerslab.com](mailto:custserv@Millerslab.com) and [customerservice@mpix.com](mailto:customerservice@mpix.com).

**How are Photos Displayed?**

Miller’s is committed to providing you with a safe environment to upload, share, market and order photos of professional photographers. Except for photos the photographer chooses to publish to a public gallery as part of the Service without password protection, photos are generally protected by a password or event number, or are published on a non-public URL, and are accessible only to people who are aware of that particular URL

## What are cookies and how does Miller’s use them?

As part of offering and providing customizable and personalized services, many Web sites use cookies to store and sometimes track information about you. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive.  We may use cookies to allow faster and easier access to your account information, monitor traffic on the site and measure traffic patterns to improve functionality.  Miller’s Web pages may in the future contain electronic images known as Web beacons  (sometimes called clear gifs or Web bugs) or other advanced technologies that are useful in the provision of services to you.  We may use such devices to verify compliance with our terms and conditions of use or with any promotions on the site.

## How does Miller’s use the information?

Miller’s primary goal in collecting information is to improve the site and provide the user with the best possible experience on the site.  We will also use your personal information to notify you of other products or services available from Miller’s and its affiliates. ****

Except as provided herein, only Miller’s and its affiliates will have access to individuals' account information. We also may do research on our users' demographics and behavior based on the information provided to us upon registration, gathered from transaction activity, from our server log files or from surveys. This research may be compiled, analyzed or sold on an anonymous aggregated basis, which does not include information that would identify you. Miller’s also may share this data with business partners or other third parties. 

## Who is collecting information?

When you are on a Miller’s site and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with Miller’s and its affiliates and service providers. If personal data is to be collected and/or maintained by any company other than Miller’s or its affiliates or service providers, we will attempt to notify you on the Site or in an updated version of this Privacy Policy. If you do not want your data to be shared, you can choose not to allow the transfer by not using that particular service. 

Please be aware that other Web sites to which we link may collect personally identifiable information about you when you visit those sites. The information practices of other Web sites linked to our Sites are not covered by this Privacy Policy. 

## With whom does Miller’s share my information?

We will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it, or under the circumstances described below. The following describes some of the ways that your information may be disclosed. 

_Data in the Aggregate_ : We may disclose “blinded” aggregated data and user statistics to prospective partners and other third parties, and for other lawful purposes.  Blinded data is data which does not identify an individual person.

_Other:_ We also may disclose account information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating Miller’s **[Terms and Conditions of Use](http://www.millerslab.com/files/policy/termsofuse.htm)** or other online or signed agreement with Millers, or that may otherwise be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) Miller’s rights or property, other Miller’s Site users or customers, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. We may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service and improve our products and services. 

We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, including packaging, delivering or mailing, answering customer questions about products or services, sending postal mail, providing investor information and processing data.  We will only provide those companies the information they need to deliver the service, and they are contractually prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.

As we continue to develop our business, we may buy or sell businesses or assets. In such transactions, confidential customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. In the event of a transaction involving the sale of some or all of Miller’s businesses, customer and site visitor information may be one of the transferred assets.

**How can I control my personal information?**

Miller’s offers its customers choices for the use and sharing of personal information.  You may contact us at [custserv@Millerslab.com](mailto:custserv@Millerslab.com) and [customerservice@mpix.com](mailto:customerservice@mpix.com).  If you wish to view, edit or delete your personal information from our database, and we will use commercially reasonable efforts to accommodate your request. 

## How does Miller’s protect financial-related information?

Keeping your personal financial information private is vitally important to us. As a matter of policy and long‑time business practice, Miller’s does not sell information provided by its customers.  Any user statistics that we may provide to prospective partners regarding financial matters are provided in the aggregate only and do not include any personally identifiable information about any individual user.   We will transfer your credit card number, bank account number or other personal information to the appropriate credit card company or bank in order to process any online payments.

## What security precautions are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of my information?

Your Miller’s Account Information and Miller’s Profile are password-protected so you have access to this personal information. We use encryption technology to protect credit card numbers, bank account numbers, passwords and registration information while they are being transferred over the public Internet.  Remember to sign out of your Miller’s account and close your browser window when you have finished your work. This is to ensure that others cannot access your account by using your computer when you are away from it. Because of the global nature of the Internet, when you give us information, that information may be sent electronically to servers outside of the country where you originally entered the information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Except as discussed above or  otherwise designated, this site does not use security encryption measures.  Therefore, information that you disclose by use of this site (as with any site that is non-secure), by posting a message or using e‑mail, potentially could be collected and used by others.  This may result in unsolicited messages from third parties or use of such information by third parties for their own purposes, legal or illegal. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, Miller’s cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we use commercially reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our systems. 

**Your Copyrights**

Miller’s respects the intellectual property rights of others. We claim no ownership rights in any image contained in any of your photo albums and will not share your images unless instructed by you or otherwise required by law or permitted under a separate agreement with you. Please note that when you share a photo album, you allow the recipients of that album to share and make that album and the photos in it available to others. For more information, see the applicable Terms of Service. 

## What else should I know about my privacy?

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose information online, that information is accessible to other customers and users. Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information.  Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online. 

When you or we end your customer relationship with us, we will treat the information we have about you as if you were still our customer.
